<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="vertical">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/aboutText"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:padding="@dimen/activity_margin"
            android:text="Nigeria Internal Security and Public Safety Alert System (NISPSAS) is a converged mobile application platform for public safety related facilities in various Ministries, Departments and Agencies (MDAs). NISPSAS is a fulfillment of internal security and public safety mandates of Ministry of Interior(MoI) and Ministry of Communications and digital Economy  converged regulation piller of  National Digital Economy Policy and Strategy(NDEPS),  which highlights the need for a single regulatory instrument that will enable government put to effective use the splitter safety and security platform operating in silos across MDAs and operationalize  Government to Citizens (G2C) and Citizens to Government (C2G) interactive pillar of  NDEPS to create safe environment for smooth implementation of presidential order 003 and 005.   NISPSAS   application was jointly developed by the Nigeria Police Force (NPF), Nigeria Security and Civil Defence Corps (NSCDC), Federal Fire Service (FFS), Nigeria Immigration Service (NIS), Nigeria Correctional Service (NCS) with operational collaboration of Department of State Services (DSS) and the office of the National Security Adviser (NSA)  utilizing development regulation pillar of National Digital Economy Strategy and indigenous proprietary software of 2TOC Solutions ltd  NISPSAS platform is primarily developed to enhance inter-agency response coordination and deepen public participation in national security, while providing one-stop shop access to  response. NISPSAS is targeted at: 	•	Enhancing a converged and immediate deployment of the splitter safety and security facilities operating in silos across MDAs in Nigeria. 	•	Increase intelligence gathering and sharing to curb banditry, terrorism, other crimes, etc. 	•	 Operationalise   sustainable intelligence  delivery from hunters, vigilantes and voluntary public  to  Nigeria Police  district intelligence desk, State police command , MOI situation room and DSS  	•	Promote inter-agencies collaboration. 	•	Lower the access barrier for persons with disabilities to access safety and security platforms. 	•	To enable public report crime when they cannot talk in the face of crime threat such as bank robbery, Road armed robbery, Kidnaping etc. 	•	Provide platform for sustainable Fire prevention  and reduce response to Fire. While controlling the use of fire extinguisher for; 	•	Improvised Explosive Device (IED) manufacturing  	•	Proliferation of small and light arms  	•	Drug trafficking etc. 	•	Provide public access to reporting looming building collapse and blocked drainage to avert flood while alerting response agencies on flood threat. 	•	Provide platform for people with disabilities to report discrimination and threat in line with disability act and convention on the right of persons with disabilities.  	•	To further promote the utilization of 112 National emergency call number  	•	To provide voluntary intelligence sharing platform between the public and the Police, Airforce etc. 	•	Provide student in higher institution of learning with platform to control cultism by reporting incidences to curb campus cultism and violence. 	•	Control fake news by verifying publisher ID as Nigeria Union of Journalist (NUJ) member 	•	Protect passengers against road crimes such as “one-chance’’, kidnapping etc. 	•	Protect  foreigners, visitors, tourist as well as investors from falling victim of fake airport  taxi and other road transport related crime 	•	Promote the campaign against rape and other gender based violence. 	•	Control crime, violence and other vices associated with fake vigilante, Hunters, Gate man etc.  	•	Measure the degree of responsiveness of agencies to public distress  	•	Measure the level of agencies preparedness to national emergencies  NISPSAS is divided into three sections namely; 	•	Intelligence gathering and sharing  	•	Emergencies Mitigation  	•	Secondary response coordination and 112 complementary  emergency reporting   NISPSAS presently consist of NINE icons performing respective functions as illustrated in the fig 1.0 diagram;  "
            android:textColor="@color/black" />

    </LinearLayout>

</ScrollView>